So, you get me to my great-great-grandpa...
所以 你到我到我的曾曾爷爷（那里）......
Then I put up your photo when I get home?
然后我放上去你的照片当我回家后
Such a smart boy!
如此一位聪明的男孩
Yes! Great idea, yes!
对好主意
One hiccup De la Cruz is a tough guy to get to...
一个小问题De la Cruz是一个棘手的家伙去接触
and I need to cross that bridge soon. Like tonight.
而我需要尽快过桥 例如 今晚
So, you got any other family here, you know?
所以你还有任何别的家人吗在这儿你知道
Someone a bit more, eh, accessible?
某人点点更呃易接近的
Um... nope.
呃 没了
Don't yank my chain, chamaco.
别扯我的链子 小子 （别唬我）
You gotta have some other family.
你肯定还有一些别的家人
Only De la Cruz.
只有De la Cruz
If you can't help me, I'll find him myself.
如果你不能帮我 我就自己去找他
Ugh. Okay, okay, kid. Fine, fine.
好 好孩子行
I'll get you to your great-great-grandpa.
我会带你去你的曾曾爷爷 (那里）